Macul, R.M. Santiago, Chile

☐ (+56) 997-950-576 | Marie ejbray@uc.cl | ☐ polirritmico | ☐ eduardo-bray

Summary

I am a developer, musician and educator graduated from the Pontificia Universidad Católica de Chile with over 15 years of experience in the fields of teaching, artistic production and technology.

I have primarily worked on integrating software and hardware solutions in artistic and educational fields. Since 2005, I have been gaining experience in GNU/Linux environments such as Gentoo, Fedora, SuSE, among others; as well as gaining advanced proficiency in office suites, audio editing, мірі, vector images and various programming languages and environments.

I am a professional with a genuine interest in continuous learning and acquiring new experiences in constructive work environments where I can contribute effectively. I am interested in being part of a team that seeks solutions that deliver value to both users and the organization itself through the creation or improvement of tools and procedures that contribute technically and humanly.

Skills_____

Programming C, Python, C#, C++, Bash, GDScript, RegEx, LaTeX, EPUB, Lua, Markdown.

Libraries and Tools GNU/Linux, Gentoo, Pandas, Pytest, Boto3, GCP, Docker, Venv, Neovim, Make, KDE, QT5, Jenkins, Jupyter,

Beautiful Soup, Logging, Argparse, Coverage, Tidy, Perl, Ableton Live/Max, SED, WPF, VM Virtual Box.

Project Management Jira, Bitbucket, Kanban, GIT, Confluence, Trello, Google Workspace, Git Hooks.

> Languages Spanish (native) and English (fluent).

Experiencia

Sunai Santiago, Chile

DIC 2022 - MAY 2023 **DESARROLLADOR PYTHON**

- Carga automática de datos en sistema ETL para API y FTP.
- Diseño y creación de tablas, queries y procedimientos PostgreSQL.
- Integración de código Python con GCP (GMail, Drive y Sheets).
- Carga automática de datos a Buckets en AWS.
- Mejora de procedimientos y creación de herramientas de automatización.
- Metodología TDD con pytest y coverage.
- Levantamiento de Pipelines en Bitbucket.
- Generación automática de reportes con PostgreSQL, C# y LaTeX bajo CLEAN architecture.
- Carga de datos y validación desde archivos xLSX locales
- · Creación de scripts Bash para procedimientos en Jenkins.

Estudio 6/8 Santiago, Chile

• Director técnico y creativo del videojuego Bakumapu (RPG).

- Programación en GDScript bajo el motor open source Godot.
- Programación en Python y librerías PyQT para herramientas internas del desarrollo.
- Diseño de metodologías de trabajo y organización en Kanban bajo plataformas Trello y GitHub.
- Desarrollo bajo TDD y CI/CD.

MUEBLISTA

DESARROLLADOR FREELANCE

Documentación LaTeX convertida automáticamente a HTML.

FONDECYT N.° 3210600 Santiago, Chile

AYUDANTE DE INVESTIGACIÓN

• Confección de Base de Datos e investigación web.

• Programación en Python, búsquedas RegEx y herramienta de web scraping.

ONG Innovacien Rancagua, Chile NOV 2021 - DIC 2021

DOCENTE DEL CURSO DE ALFABETIZACIÓN DIGITAL

• Clases de manejo básico de sistemas Windows, Microsoft Office y navegación web.

Confección y diseño de muebles y controladores

• Confección de controladores MIDI de baja latencia con Arduino (C, C++).

• Diseño de muebles y modelación 3D en SketchUp.

15 DE JUNIO DE 2023

Santiago, Chile

ENE 2018 - presente

MAR 2021 - presente

AGO 2021 - DIC 2021

Compañía de Teatro La Recogida

MÚSICO, COMPOSITOR, LUTHIER E INTÉRPRETE.

Santiago, Chile
JUL 2012 - DIC 2014

- Desarrollo de controlador MIDI inalámbrico para samples y efectos en tiempo real.
- Pedal controlador Bluetooth para visualización de partituras.

Orquestas, Agrupaciones y Ensambles Varios

Santiago, Chile ENE 2005 - presente

• Sistemas de sincronización MIDI vía LAN entre Ableton Live y Resolume Arena para visuales y audio SFX en tiempo real.

• Programación MIDI y plugins MAX.

INTÉRPRETE DE BATERÍA Y PERCUSIÓN

- Percusionista en la оғи, озля, Ensamble de Percusión імис, Musicales de la Pastoral ис.
- Proyectos independientes y variadas agrupaciones de música popular y experimental.

Varios colegios Santiago, Chile

PROFESOR DE MÚSICA

ABR 2015 - DIC 2019

- Colegio SS. CC. Manquehue (2015-2019).
- · Colegio Altamira (2018).
- · Complejo Educacional Esperanza (2016).

Education

PUC (Pontificia Universidad Católica de Chile)

Santiago, Chile

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN EDUCATION

MAR 2015 - JAN 2016

- Seminar research on musical learning of students through Information and Communication Technologies.
- High School Teacher in Music Education.
- Graduated with distinction.

PUC (Pontificia Universidad Católica de Chile)

Santiago, Chile

MAR 2005 - JUL 2014

BACHELOR'S DEGREE IN MUSIC

VARIOUS COMMUNITIES

- Advanced music performer in Percussion
- Technical courses in advanced programming as part of the Minor in Programming and Informatics.
- Treasurer and Vice President of the Music Student Association (CEEM).

Actividad Extracurricular_

Ebook Editor Int.

• Digitization of books and automated ocr process correction.

Digitization of books and automated OCR process correction.
 Layout design of books in EPUB, XHTML formats using CSS in Sigil.

- Development of tools and plugins to facilitate the correction processes (Python and PyQT5).
- Creation of Inkscape video tutorials for image vectorization.

GNU/Linux Groups and Forums

Int.

2013 - Present

2005 - Present

PARTICIPATION AS AN OPEN SOURCE SOFTWARE USER

- · Bug reporting and creation of diff patches.
- Advising and supporting users of Gentoo Linux systems.
- Publishing tutorials and configurations.

15 DE JUNIO DE 2023

2